liveshare.com 2010-12-08

# Liveshare by Cooliris | Legal - Privacy Policy

Cooliris takes your privacy seriously. We will not share Personally Identifiable Information about you except as described in this Privacy Policy. We, Cooliris, Inc., have designed software to enhance your ability to discover free content streamed from the web and our content providers along with advertisements that are most interesting to you. To do this, we request some information from you and automatically collect other information about your usage of our services. While this allows us to offer you the best service possible, we understand the critical importance of personal privacy and want you to understand how we handle your personal information. This document outlines the types of information Cooliris Products (all products and services provided by Cooliris, Inc.) collect from the user and how we store and use this data.

## Why We Collect Information

We collect information in connection with your use of Cooliris Products in order to improve and personalize your experience with Cooliris Products as you search and discover content that is most interesting to you from third party websites and content providers. In some cases, this information is also used to serve relevant and interesting content and advertising streamed through Cooliris Products from third party websites. The types of information we collect from our users are described below.

## What Information We Collect

  * Registration Information: If and when you register for the Cooliris Service, we ask for basic registration information, such as your name, age, sex, likes/dislikes, a username and password, which you choose, and an e-mail address for Cooliris support. You may send messages to third party e-mail addresses and you may also enter in certain passwords and user names for third party sites and services. We use this Personally Identifiable Information ("PII") to suggest content, to deliver advertisements, to learn about our audience, including through non-personally identifiable statistics (e.g. percentage of male viewers aged 35-44), and to apply what we've learned to improve the service.
  * Anonymous Data: When you use Cooliris Products, we may collect technical and navigational information, such as computer browser type, operating system information, Internet protocol address, queries sent through the Cooliris Service, geographic information, third party sites from which you download Cooliris Products and its components, Internet domain names from which you launch Cooliris Products and its components, statistics for messages sent through the Cooliris Service, and frequency and time spent in the Cooliris Service. We use cookies, log file information, and clear gifs to collect this Non-Personally Identifiable Information ("Non-PII").
  *     * Cookies Information: In connection with your use of Cooliris Products, we may install a cookie on your computer to help customize your experience in the Cooliris Products, including our websites. A cookie is a piece of data from your browser that identifies you as a unique user and lets Cooliris help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the Cooliris Software. A cookie does not collect personal information about you. Cooliris uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser's directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. If you do not wish to have cookies set on your computer, you can configure your browser to refuse cookies. This, however, may disable certain services in Cooliris Products.
    * Log File Information: In connection with your use of Cooliris Products, we may collect log file information automatically reported by your browser each time you access a web page, and active client log file information regarding user interactions. When you register with or use the Cooliris Service, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information.
    * Clear Gifs Information: In connection with your use of Cooliris Products, we may employ clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our users anonymously within our web properties. No Personally Identifiable Information from your Cooliris account is collected using these clear gifs. In addition, we may also use clear gifs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients. The information is used to enable more accurate reporting, improve the effectiveness of our marketing, and make the Cooliris Products better for our users.

## How We Use The Information We Collect

  * Non-Personally Identifiable Information: Cooliris only uses Non-PII data (such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure to improve our product, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. As part of this use of information, we may provide aggregate information to our partners about how our customers, collectively, use Cooliris Products. We may share Non-PII with interested third parties to help them understand the usage patterns for certain Cooliris services.

  * Personally Identifiable Information: Cooliris will NOT rent or sell your PII to others. Solely for the purpose of providing services to you may Cooliris share your PII with third parties. If we do this, such third parties' use of your information will be bound by this Privacy Policy. We may store personal information in locations outside the direct control of Cooliris (for instance, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers).

You may decline to provide PII through Cooliris, in which case Cooliris may not be able to provide certain personalized services to you, including but not limited to our sharing features. You can review and correct your PPI that Cooliris has stored, if any, by contacting us directly at [privacy@cooliris.com](mailto:privacy@cooliris.com).

PII refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains. This includes information that is used in a way that is personally identifiable, including linking it with identifiable information from other sources, or from which other PII can easily be derived, including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number, and email address.

Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, Cooliris will not disclose PII, if collected at all, to any third party unless required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law, comply with legal process served on us or our affiliates, or investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities; (b) to enforce our Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, or to protect the security or integrity of our site; and (c) to exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Cooliris, our users or others.

As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or dissolution.

## Third Party Advertisements and Links

Cooliris allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements on the Cooliris site and through the Cooliris service. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on Cooliris. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content.

Cooliris does not provide any PII to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent. However, please note that if an advertiser asks Cooliris to show an advertisement to a certain audience and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks. The Cooliris Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such advertisers.

We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site nor the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Web site to another Web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other Web site, including those that have a link on our Web site, is subject to that Web site's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

## Security

We continue to store your PII for as long as it is necessary to provide you the Cooliris Service, and we periodically destroy PII in accordance with our company policies, including when it is no longer essential to our ability to offer you the same high quality service. In most cases, we will keep one archival copy of your information for the uses set forth in this Privacy Policy.

Cooliris uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your PII. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Cooliris and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of PII, Cooliris makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such PII may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you access to your account. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information, and for controlling access to your email communications from Cooliris, at all times.

In the event that PII is compromised as a result of a breach of security, Cooliris will promptly notify those persons whose PII has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise required by applicable law.

## Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Cooliris does not knowingly collect or solicit PII from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not send any PII about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any PII to or on Cooliris. In the event that we learn that we have collected PII from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that PII as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any PII from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [privacy@cooliris.com](mailto:privacy@cooliris.com).

## Notification Procedures

It is our policy to provide notifications, whether such notifications are required by law or are for marketing or other business related purposes, to you via email notice, written or hard copy notice, or through conspicuous posting of such notice on our website, as determined by Cooliris in its sole discretion. We reserve the right to determine the form and means of providing notifications to you, provided that you may opt out of certain means of notification as described in this Privacy Policy.

## Access to Personal Information

Cooliris allows you to access certain information about yourself for the purpose of viewing, and in certain situations, updating that information via our website. The types of information that you can access and update will change as the Cooliris Products change.

## Policy Changes

The effective date of this Privacy Policy is February 25, 2010.

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time.

## Questions or Concerns

If you have any questions or concerns regarding Cooliris' Privacy Policy, please send us a detailed message to [privacy@cooliris.com](mailto:privacy@cooliris.com). We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.
